http://www.castlemcculloch.com/privacy-policy.html

HomeContact UsEvent InquiryPreferred Vendor InquiryWedding ShowReformatted Wedding Expo - COVID PrecautionsEvent TypesWedding & ReceptionsPrivate EventsCorporate Meetings/EventsPreferred VendorsBakersCakes By BCurbside CakeryBeauty ServicesReflections Hair SalonCaterersCulinary Visions CateringRosa Mae's CateringFloral DesignersBennett's Baskets And BowsMusic & Entertainment DJ Paul CordtsDr. PiperWorld Tour DJBorn To DJOfficiant/ClergyWedding Minister-Ron GrilloPhotographersBert Reed PhotographyMagnolia Ridge PhotographyBrian Anthony PhotographyPhoto RAMIT ProductionsSnap Post PhotoboothAssociate Vendors Black Tie Formal WearHotelsMary KayVintage Sound & LightModern WoodmenAmethyst VacationsVenue Specifications Virtual TourFAQ'sReviews & NewsTheatre Summer CampThe Castle Presents Events
It is Castle McCulloch’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website.Website VisitorsLike most website operators, Castle McCulloch collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Castle McCulloch’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Castle McCulloch’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Castle McCulloch may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.Castle McCulloch also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on WordPress.com blogs. Castle McCulloch only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that blog commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog where the comment was left.Gathering of Personally-Identifying InformationCertain visitors to Castle McCulloch’s website choose to interact with Castle McCulloch in ways that require Castle McCulloch to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Castle McCulloch gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. Those who engage in transactions with Castle McCulloch are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Castle McCulloch collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Castle McCulloch. Castle McCulloch does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying InformationCastle McCulloch discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Castle McCulloch’s behalf or to provide services available at Castle McCulloch’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Castle McCulloch’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Castle McCulloch will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Castle McCulloch discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Castle McCulloch believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Castle McCulloch, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of Castle McCulloch website and have supplied your email address, Castle McCulloch may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Castle McCulloch and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Castle McCulloch takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.CookiesA cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Castle McCulloch uses cookies to help Castle McCulloch identify and track visitors, their usage of Castle McCulloch  website, and their website access preferences. Castle McCulloch visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Castle McCulloch’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Castle McCulloch’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.Business TransfersIf Castle McCulloch, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Castle McCulloch goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Castle McCulloch may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.AdsAds appearing on our website may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Castle McCulloch and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.Privacy Policy ChangesAlthough most changes are likely to be minor, Castle McCulloch may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Castle McCulloch’s sole discretion. Castle McCulloch encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
View on Mobile
